Hi!
This Lindsay Colbus from Lindsay Colbus Accessories.
I'm going to eventually show you several examples of what to wear and what not to wear on this first date.
I also quickly want to talk about what day of the week that you're going on a date.
Some dates might occur after the workday.
A 6 o'clock date on a weekday.
Other dates might be on a Friday or a Saturday night, or even like a Sunday football date at a bar.
There are so many different variations.
I'm going to try to show you how you can wear something to work and transition that same outfit into an appropriate date for after work.
Not only are we going to look at examples of how to dress for a hot Saturday night date or a hot Friday night date.
I'm going to try to show you how one outfit can actually get you through the work day, and still get you to wherever you may be meeting your date in one outfit so you don't have to change.
You don't have to go through the stress of packing a bag and taking it to work with you.